{
  "LevelId": 13,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 121,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "FLEXIBLE",
      "question": "Adaptable or easily bent"
    },
    {
      "id": 122,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BICYCLER",
      "question": "a person who rides a two-wheeled vehicle powered by pedaling"
    },
    {
      "id": 123,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BALLYARD",
      "question": "refers to a field or stadium used for playing baseball"
    },
    {
      "id": 124,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "AMERICAN",
      "question": "describes something related to the United States of America"
    },
    {
      "id": 125,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "HIJACKED",
      "question": "unauthorized seizure of a vehicle, aircraft, or vessel"
    },
    {
      "id": 126,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "VARIABLE",
      "question": "Subject to change"
    },
    {
      "id": 127,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "NORTHERN",
      "question": "Region higher on a map"
    },
    {
      "id": 128,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "AIRPORTS",
      "question": "Places for takeoffs and landings"
    },
    {
      "id": 129,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "ALLEGROS",
      "question": "Quick-paced musical movements"
    },
    {
      "id": 130,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BETRAYED",
      "question": "Acted against trust"
    },
    {
      "id": 131,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "BLACKBERRY",
      "question": "Edible dark-purple fruit"
    }
  ]
}